我要订一束玫瑰
I'd like to order roses, a dozen.
在卡片上写 "我昨晚很开心"就好
Just put: "I had a great time last night" on the card.
别署名 能否找个人帮忙
Don't sign it. Actually, is there anyway to get someone
在卡片上印上个唇印?
to put a lipstick kiss on the gift card?
这听着很有趣啊
That sounds interesting.
更像是勾引
More like contagious.
她都送了一个礼拜了...
She sends almost one a week...
每次都是不同的男人
each time to a different guy.
这是最后一个吗?
Is that the last one?
我实在等不及想出去了
I'm itching to get going tonight.
工作了一天...我实在是需要放松一下
Rough day at work...I need to burn off some steam.
就等着最后一个了
Just one more.
你好 我想订束花
Hi. I'm calling to order flowers
葬礼用的
for a funeral.
附上一张素雅一些的卡片就行
I just need something simple on the card.
但愿不是 "我昨晚很开心"
Hope it's not "I had a great time last night."
就写 "墨菲 你和你朋友觉得
Just put: "Did you and your friend think
我找不到你们了是吗? 我跟你说过
I wouldn't find you, Murphy? Told you I'd get you
天涯海角我也要找到你"
when you least expected it."
这是个恶作剧吧...
If that's a joke...
NCIS 第九季第十五集
- 抱歉... - 难以置信!
- Sorry... - Unbelievable!
你看哭泣的游戏了?
You finally saw The Crying Game?
- 没! 我得了张超速罚单 - 哦
- No! I got a speeding ticket. - Ooh.
你知道这代表什么嘛 麦基?
You know what that means, McGee?
- 交通系统很管用 -我只是在限速范围内
- The system works. - I was barely going
超了一点点而已
over the limit.
让我瞧瞧
Let me see.
这上面可是说你在限速40的路上跑的80啊
It says you were doing 80 in a 40.
又不是一直跑的80
Not the entire time.
你跟他说你是个联邦探员了吗?
You tell him you're a federal agent?
- 什么意思? - 呃 有时候吧
- Excuse me? - Well, sometimes,
如果他们知道你是联邦探员的话 他们会另眼相看
if they know, they look the other way.
"噢 不好意思这是我的警徽"
"Oh, that's not my wallet."
- 等等 你经常这么干? - 告诉你个小秘密
- Wait. You do that often? - With one notable exception.
在过去的17年里我都没有拿过罚单
I haven't gotten a speeding ticket in 17 years.
也没有因为违章停车被罚过
Or paid for parking,
足球比赛也没有...
football games...
这就是个灰色领域
It's a gray area.
有时候我甚至还
Sometimes I even get
能吃到免费甜品和咖啡
my donuts and coffee for free.
我可不觉得吉布斯同意你这么干
I do not think Gibbs would approve.
只要吉布斯不知道 不就行了
What Gibbs doesn't know won't hurt him.
我不知道什么 蒂诺佐?
What don't I know, DiNozzo?
嗯 姬娃被开罚单了
Um, Ziva got a speeding ticket.
还有我...有时候有免费咖啡可以喝
And I... sometimes get coffee for free.
但我给的小费很多
But I tip big.
好吧 来打吧
All right, let's have it.
走吧 发现海军上尉的尸体
Let's go. Dead navy captain.
你觉不觉得他被吉布斯
Do you ever get the feeling that
拍脑勺的时候特别享受啊?
he enjoys being smacked in the head?
我宁愿想都不要想
I'd rather not think about it.
两枪
Two shots.
嗯 动静肯定不小
Yep. They must have made some noise.
的确
They did.
有几个 呃 几个目击者听见了枪响
Several, uh, witnesses heard the gunshots.
在大街上发现了弹壳
Found the brass in the street.
就没有人报警吗?
No one called the police?
姬娃 在这地方 枪战可不是
Gunshots aren't exactly news
什么新闻
in the this neighborhood, Ziva.
清洁工发现了尸体
Cleaning lady found the body.
打电话报警 警察就找我们就来了
She called the cops, they called us.
保险箱被撬了
Safe's picked.
这是什么? 指甲?
What are these? Fingernails?
这保险柜里的东西肯定很重要
Somebody was nervous about something.
抱歉我来晚了
Sorry I was late.
我得等到帕摩先生办完事回来
Been waiting for Mr. Palmer to return from an errand.
-我才能过来 -什么情况?
- I had to leave without him. - What errand?
布瑞娜打电话来了
Brrrreena called.
他们筹备婚礼时请的那个
The wedding caterer they planned on using
宴会承包人出差了
had gone out of business.
那哭声能把死人哭活了
The sobs almost woke the dead.
那她真是挺伤心的?
She pretty upset?
哭的那个人可不是她
She wasn't the one crying.
现在什么情况?
What do we have here?
嗯 躺在这的是杰克・瓦里斯上校
Well, over here, you got Captain Jack Wallace and,
那么 躺在这儿的是他朋友德克斯特・墨菲
of course, our friend here is Dexter Murphy.
看起来像是起入室抢劫案
Looks like an open-and-shut robbery.
- 我猜你还会来个"不过" - 呃 不过听这个
- Do I suspect a "but"? - Uh, but this.
你好 我想订束花
Hi. I'm calling to order flowers
葬礼上用的
for a funeral.
附上一张素雅一些的卡片就行
I just need something simple on the card.
就写 "墨菲 你和你朋友觉得
Just put: "Did you and your friend think I wouldn't
我找不到你们了是吗? 我跟你说过
find you, Murphy? Told you I'd get you
天涯海角我也会找到你"
when you least expected it."
某个男人的留言
A man of his word.
是啊
Yeah.
我大概明白了
So I can see.
能初步断定案件发生的原因
The preliminary cause of death is obvious,
但是我还是...
but I think I will...
保留意见
reserve judgment.
-看看我们发现了什么? - 达克
- What do we have here? - Duck.
天呐 Duckman内衣
Holy undergarments, Duckman.
是我想的那样吗?
Is that what I think it is?
他是杰克・瓦里斯上校
His name is Captain Jack Wallace.
他是伊战老兵 还有就是
He's a decorated Iraq veteran, and he's also
他是一个现实生活中的超级英雄
a Real-Life Superhero.
- 一个啥? -他们这样称呼他
- A what? - That's what they're called.
- 谁们? -他们自己
- By who? - By themselves.
他们没有真正的神奇力量
They don't claim to have actual superpowers.
肯定的 他们真有的话那才叫诡异了呢
Right, 'cause that would be weird.
不 他们只是一个活动团体
No, they're really just community activists.
穿上服装 监视社区
They put on costumes and do neighborhood watches,
提供公共服务 有时候还组织募捐
community service, sometimes even fund-raising.
- 还真不赖 是吧? -嘿 我说他们组织生日派对吗?
- Pretty cool, huh? - Hey, do they do birthday parties?
监视社区是Solanum负责进行的
Neighborhood watches were Solanum's specialty.
- 谁? - 德克斯特・墨菲
- Who? - Dexter Murphy,
那个店主... 他扮的超级英雄叫Solanum
the store owner... his Superhero name was Solanum.
瓦里斯上校的代号是 Code队长
Captain Wallace went by Captain Code.
他是负责居民楼内的密码情况
His specialty building-code violations.
我还发现他们在保卫地球超级英雄网站上注册了
I found them registered at EarthSuperHeroUnion.com
他们也有网站?
They have a Web site, too?
哦 这就是他们的网站 还有他们的活动小组
Oh, there's Web sites, there's community groups,
他们甚至讨论是否成立一个裁判小组
there's even talk of creating a sanctioning body,
就像NBA一样
like the NBA.
不过 当一个现实生活种的超级英雄也是非常危险的
Of course, being an RLSH can be dangerous, too.
尤其是 当涉及到一些犯罪行为
Especially if you're getting involved with the criminal stuff...
像是非法涂鸦
going after
还有盗窃行为
graffiti taggers, muggers.
所以 当他们有难了 他们就打电话报警?
So, when these guys get in trouble, they call the cops?
有些会 有些不会
Some do, some don't.
那他们还是挺机警
So, they're like vigilantes.
是莽撞吧
Nerd vigilantes.
问题是 他们是不是因为这些才被杀死的?
Question is, did it get them killed?
语音留言很明显是杀手在暗示
The voice mail clearly indicates the killer
他要来寻仇了
was seeking revenge.
为了什么?
For what?
我去查电话记录
The phone records.
-我去查上级指挥官 -我去查电子邮箱 谷歌邮箱 微博
- A commanding officer. - E-mails, G-mails, Twitter.
米勒小姐 我们就这么说定了?
So, do we have a deal or not, Ms. Miller?
呃 这要看你的探员了
Well, that's gonna depend on your agent.
这可不太好啊
That doesn't sound good.
吉布斯探员
Agent Gibbs,
-我向你介绍... -还在
- I'd like you to meet... - Still working
晚报工作? - 国际新闻部
for the Evening Tribune? - The Globe.
你们认识?
You two know each other?
天呐 告诉我你们没结过婚
Oh, please tell me that you weren't married.
没有
No.
但是我们的确有一段过去
But we go back.
哦 好吧
Oh, good.
这就让事情变得更简单了
That should make things easier.
也许更糟
Or worse.
我会处理好的 可以开始了吗?
I'll manage. Shall we?
瓦里斯上校两天前
Captain Wallace called me
往报社打电话 想跟我见一面
at my paper two days ago, wanted to meet.
- 为了什么? -不能说
- About what? - Wouldn't say.
不过那套超级英雄的服装肯定暗示着一些什么
But that superhero costume sure says something.
- 我什么都没说 - 别忘了 我可是记者
- I didn't tell her. - I am a reporter, remember?
他想告诉你什么?
So, what's the story?
瓦里斯正在接手一个非能源部
Wallace ran a classified program
下达的秘密任务
out of the Department of Energy,
护送核废料到热点地区
securing rogue nuclear materials in hot-spot areas.
那里对钱苏联铀的需求量很大
There's a big demand for old Soviet uranium.
机密文件 里昂
File's classified, Leon.
这文件是她的 可不是我的
That file is hers. It's not mine.
记者的好处
Reporter.
如果爆出一个这么重大的消息
Press is gonna have a field day with this one.
你肯定能想象出头条会是什么样的
I'm sure you can imagine the headline.
嗯
Hmm.
"海军军官在护送核武器途中
"Navy officer in charge of nukes
被发现身着超级英雄服装暴毙而亡"
found dead in superhero costume."
很拗口 不过我喜欢
Wordy, but I like it.
我不喜欢
I don't.
不管怎么说
However,
米勒小姐同意在你破案之前
Ms. Miller has agreed to hold off
不发表相关文章
till you conduct your investigation.
你上司希望你能发现
Your director hopes that you'll find something
该怎么说 更出彩的东西来
that paints things in a more, shall we say, favorable light.
作为交换我们会给你第一手的资料
In exchange for first dibs on any info we do uncover.
哦 还有NCIS的线人 以便给我所需要的消息
Oh, plus a liaison from NCIS to keep me in the loop.
吉布斯探员 就是你了
And you're that liaison, Agent Gibbs.
我相信你的专业水准
I trust that you'll handle the matter professionally.
我的老天爷!
Oh, my God!
艾比 不介意我在这儿躲起来歇一会儿吧?
Abby, do you mind if I hide down here?
麦基快把我搞疯了...
McGee is driving me crazy with all...
小野猫 这又是哪一出?
What's new, pussycat?
你听见我说的了吧
I guess you heard.
呃 关于现实生活种的超级英雄?
Um, about the Real- Life Superheroes?
喂!我可是为了联系上
Hello! I've been trying to meet
Cataonic花了几个月的时间啊
Catatonic for, like, months.
他拯救动物 大部分是猫
He rescues animals, mostly cats.
他在庇护所里就像
And he's like a rock star
摇滚明星一样火
in the shelter community.
现在我们法庭需要一个摇滚明星
Right now we need a rock star in the forensic community.
我正在研究你在保险柜找到的
I am making some progress on the chewed fingernails
那些凶手咬下来的指甲
that you found at the safe.
可能 就是 有的...
Maybe, like, some...
有的凶手开锁时比较紧张才会咬指甲
some nervous murderer trying to pick a lock
我正在做DNA配对 不过...
I'm running the DNA now, but...
我有重大发现
my big find was online.
我发现这个徽章 看起来很眼熟
I noticed this insignia, and it looked familiar.
然后我想起来我是从哪儿看来的了
And then I remembered where I knew it from.
六个月前一场酒吧斗殴事件
There was a bar fight uploaded to CyberVid
被传到在CyberVid网
six months ago.
我可不想找麻烦 你想怎么样?
I don't want any trouble! You don't want any trouble?
不! 真糟糕 是你找到的
No! Too bad 'cause you found it!
你个傻子 是你找到的! 让他走吧!
No, punk, you found it! Let him go!
嘿 老兄 放开我 你个神经病!
Hey, man, let go of me, you freak!
瓦里斯和墨菲拦住了那个肇事者
Wallace and Murphy stopped the bad guy.
耶! 后来这个视频火了
Yay! So, the video went viral,
他们就变成了当地人们的英雄了
and they became local heroes.
那个醉鬼...就那个看起来像醉鬼的
The drunk idiot... Looks like a drunk idiot.
好像很忌恨的样子
Maybe he's holding a grudge.
你查到他的身份了吗?
You got an I.D.?
呃 我还无法通过面部识别查到这个人
Well, I haven't had any hits on facial recognition.
那么到底是谁拍下的这个视频?
So, who shot this video?
是一个名叫ICU的用户上传的
It was uploaded by a user called ICU.
我追踪不到这个人的真实身份
Had trouble tracking that back to an actual person.
不过不管是谁 他肯定费劲了心思
Whoever did this went to a lot of trouble
隐藏他的身份
to keep his identity hidden.
走着瞧
Keep looking.
原来你在这儿
There you are.
哈! 是啊
Ha! Yeah.
哇哦
Wow.
你也在这儿
There you are.
你来干嘛?
What are you doing there?
吉布斯探员派你担任瓦里斯案子的联络员
Agent Gibbs assigned you to be my liaison on the Wallace case.
噢
Oh.
联络员是什么意思?
What do you mean, "liaison"?
你现在是个记者
You're a reporter now.
我们不需要...和记者联络
We don't... liaise with reporters.
但是现在你必须这么做
You do now.
吉布斯可没和我说起这事
Gibbs didn't say anything to me about this.
嘿 托尼 托尼 托尼!
Hey, Tony, Tony, Tony!
吉布斯让我转达你...
Gibbs wanted me to tell you that...
噢 你好
Oh. Hello.
你好
Hi.
所以...
So...
我们要怎么办?
what do we do now?
托尼 我也对这件事很不满
Well, I'm not happy about it, either, Tony,
但我希望你拿出你的专业精神来
but I expect you to be professional.
我一直很敬业
Always.
我们之间没必要搞得像敌人一样
It's not like we're enemies.
对啊 我邀请你参加过圣诞聚餐
Exactly. I did invite you to Christmas brunch,
而且我们曾经订了婚
and at one point in our lives, we were engaged to be married.
太强悍了
Meow.
我想再打个招呼...
Hi... again.
我叫艾比
I'm Abby.
我叫温迪
Wendy.
温迪!
Wendy!
那个前未婚妻 温迪
Wendy the ex-fiancée.
麦基 他们来了 他们来了!
McGee, here they come, here they come!
等等...
Hold on...
头儿! 我们能不能谈一谈?
Boss! Can I talk to you for a second?
噢 温迪 穿过那扇门 走到底
Uh, Wendy, conference room is just through that door,
就是会议室 麻烦你先走
there at the end. Thanks.
让我当温迪的联络员? 你想什么呢?
I'm Wendy's liaison? What were you thinking?
你就跟她说事情有变 我...
You were there when it went south. I c...
不行
Sorry.
抱歉
我们要专业地对待这事儿吧
Aren't we professional.
当然
That's what we are.
恩 我们从基本的开始
Okay, let's start with the basics.
你以前和瓦里斯相识吗? 不
Have you ever spoken with Wallace before? no
知道他为何在死前打给你?
Have any idea what his call was about?
不知道
Nope.
你为什么邀请我去圣诞聚餐?
Why'd you invite me to Christmas brunch?
我以为看到你会很高兴
Thought it might be nice to see you.
可能我错了
I may have been wrong.
- 轮到我了 - 轮到你干嘛?
- My turn. - Your turn what?
我要问几个问题
I get to ask some questions.
那是我和旺斯的协议
That's my deal with Vance.
瓦利斯上校有精神病史吗?
Does Captain Wallace have a history of mental illness?
没有
No.
那你们海军知道他在偷偷扮英雄吗?
Was the navy aware that he was moonlighting as a... Superhero?
不知道
No.
你什么时候开始穿上千元的西装?
Since when did you start wearing thousand-dollar suits?
你什么时候不再教4岁的小孩子唱
Since when did you stop teaching four-year-olds how to sing
神龙帕夫 继而转型成超人妻子?
"Puff the Magic Dragon" and start channeling Lois Lane?
人总是会变的
People change.
是啊 他们是的
Yes, they do.
我没有错
I wasn't wrong.
很高兴能见到你
It is nice to see you.
我也是
It's nice to see you, too.
恩
Mm.
得了吧 这是我发明的
Come on. I invented that.
呃 我们来只是想跟你说
Well, we just wanted to let you know
艾比还无法确定上传那个打架视频的
that Abby's still unable to identify the user
用户的身份
who uploaded that fight video.
噢
Oh.
吉布斯希望我们调查下周围居民
Gibbs wants us to canvas the neighborhood.
看有没有人认识那个酒鬼
See if anyone knows who the drunk idiot is.
噢 那个人我不认识 但我知道那个视频
Oh, I don't know him, but that video
是一个叫克莱恩斯・托百特的人拍的
was shot by a man name Clarence Tobett.
本地信托基金的宠儿
Local trust-fund baby,
经营反对帮派的业务
runs an anti-gang outreach program.
- 我是个记者 - 记者
- Reporter. - Reporter.
他总是会写一些东西
He's always calling the paper,
以引起民众注意
trying to drum up publicity.
谢谢
Thank you.
恩 记得告诉我你们的新发现
Hm. Let me know what you find.
她人很好啊
She is cute.
打住
Stop it.
你的前未婚妻很可爱啊
Your ex-fiancée's really cute.
和我想的大相径庭啊
But I would expect no less.
这么多年后相见 感觉很陌生吧?
Must be strange seeing her again after all these years, huh?
尤其是在她离婚后?
Especially with her divorced?
你居然不吭声
Almost as strange as you not talking.
我在工作 你投入点 谢谢了
I'm working. You should try it. Thank you.
你是克莱恩斯 托百特?
Clarence Tobett?
你们是?
Who wants to know?
海军罪案调查处!
NCIS!
我们在找拍这段视频的人
We're looking for the man who shot this video.
你们怎么找到我的?
How'd you find me?
我花了好大劲儿隐藏身份
I work very hard to keep my true identity a secret.
噢 咔嚓!
Oh, snap!
你是他们中的一个!
You're one of them!
如果你是指现实生活超级英雄 那就对了
If you mean Real-Life Superhero, then, yes.
让我猜猜 你是ICU?
Let me guess. ICU?
是 这也是你们过来
That's right, 'cause that's where you go
调查我的原因吧
if you mess with me.
鉴于我们...
Since we're...
是同行
coworkers,
我会充分配合你们
you will have my complete cooperation.
是 是我拍了那段视频
Yes, I shot the video.
我在当罪犯诱饵时遇到这起事件的
I came upon the fight when I was out on bait patrol.
罪犯诱饵?
Bait patrol?
对 一种专业的引诱打击罪犯的策略
Yes, it's a standard crime-fighting tactic.
我们中的某个人...别 别 别
One of us... No, no, no, no, no, no.
...扮成诱饵 等待
...acts as bait, and waits
罪犯上钩
for someone to cause trouble.
他们一旦有所行动 我们就进行反击
When they do, we give it to them.
- 克莱恩斯! - 噢!
- Clarence! - Oh!
我什么时候允许你把汤姆借走了?
What did I tell you about borrowing Tom?
- 我... - 不!
- I... - No!
不 不 不!
No, no, no!
佩顿小姐说你们是NCIS的人
Miss Peyton said you're from NCIS.
他犯了什么事?
What did he do now?
爸 没事
Nothing, Dad.
事实上 是你打断了我们 我们在说正事
In fact, if you'll excuse us, this is business.
不 不 我在做的才叫正事
No, no. Business is what I do.
而你只是在花我给你的钱而已
I buy real estate, you just take it up.
25岁的人了还像5岁小孩一样!
Acting like you're five, instead of 25!
他到底干了些什么?
What did he do?
噢 他其实是在帮我指认这个人
Oh, he was actually helping us identify someone.
我记得这个人
I remember him.
虽然我不知道他的名字
I don't have a name,
但他逃走的时候我记下了他的牌照
but I got his license plate when he fled.
呃 部分车牌号
Well, some of it.
够了 就此打住 不许再把汤姆借走!
All right, I've heard enough. No more Tom!
他是个强手 不能来陪你浪费时间
The guy's got a Bronze Star, for Pete's sake.
他才是真正的英雄
He's a real hero.
他就是气我
He's just pissed because I refuse
不接手家族产业
to go into the family business.
我猜也是这样
I can relate.
克莱恩斯?
Clarence?
- 克莱恩斯! -干嘛?
- Clarence! - What?
- 车牌号? - 噢
- License plate? - Oh.
三个数字
Three numbers.
超强记忆该不会是你的超级能力吧
I guess super memory isn't one of your superpowers.
随你取笑 但我做的事是正紧事
Make all the fun you want, but what I do is important.
上个礼拜我成功说服一个孩子脱离犯罪组织
I talked a kid out of a gang just last week.
我知道我们的服装很傻逼 但这只是个噱头而已
I know the costumes seem silly, but they're just a gimmick.
服装是为了缓解紧张的气氛
They help defuse tense situations.
我不知道Code队长的真实身份
Look, I don't know Captain Code's true identity.
我觉得我们还是继续让它是个谜比较好
It's best that we keep them secret, even from each other,
我听到了一些关于他的流言
but I did hear a rumor that something happened to him.
不知道会不会对你们有帮助
I don't know if this helps you, but
他说他遇到了情况
he had mentioned that he was onto something.
不过没说清楚是什么事 反正...
He didn't say what, but it...
他很担心
had him worried.
这是我的名片
Here's my card.
如果你们想要那种t恤的话
I have T-shirts, too,
我也有
if you want them.
谢谢 谢谢你了
Thank you. Thank you.
恩
Mm-hmm.
我年轻那会 也有真实生活中的超级英雄
We had our own real-life superhero in my youth.
他把自己叫做The Fox 是个最早的环境学家的名字
He called himself "The Fox," one of the first environmentalists.
有一次 他从污水区
Once, he collected 50 gallons of sewage
收集了50加仑的废水
that was destroying a lake, broke into the...
把它们泼到了
the offending corporation's offices,
排出这些污水公司的办公大厅
and dumped it in their lobby.
每个小孩都在幻想能快点长大
Every child fantasizes about growing up
变成一个超级英雄
and becoming a superhero,
但是你确实做到了
but you actually did it.
真厉害啊
Impressive.
达克 我可不会这么夸他
Not the word I would have chosen, Duck.
你查到了什么?
What do you got?
呃 我觉得这两个人应该是
Uh, I think we can assume that both victims
死于枪杀
died of their gunshot wounds.
这很显然
Not surprised.
是啊 让人意外的是我在瓦里斯上校
Yeah, well, the surprise came
身上发现的伤口数量
from the number of injuries I found on Captain Wallace.
他的下巴被打伤两次
He broke his jaw twice.
有多处刀伤
He has scars from numerous knife wounds
甚至有枪弹的擦痕
and even has a bullet graze.
他在街头打斗过
Doing a little street fighting.
是啊 大概吧
Yeah, well, presumably.
他很认真地在做保卫工作
He took his role as a vigilante quite seriously.
拜托 达克
Come on, Duck.
我想你应该不认同他们的做法吧?
I take it, you do not approve?
达克 这不是他们该做的事
Duck, it's not their job.
他们有可能会受伤
They could get hurt.
杰瑟罗 他们大多数都受伤了
Jethro, most of them already have been.
这些打击罪犯的人除了爱看漫画
Aside from their...their love of comic books,
还有个共性 他们愿意
what most of these crime-fighters have in common
牺牲自己
is being victims of violent crime themselves.
付出名誉或是生命
Or abuse or tragedy.
你看看瓦里斯上校的资料
I mean, take a look at Captain Wallace.
他妻子在分娩时死亡
His wife died in childbirth.
之后 她的女儿在购物商场遭遇天台塌陷而死
And then, his daughter died when a balcony collapsed in a shopping mall.
麦基说他可是违反建筑条例的老手
McGee said his specialty was building-code violations.
这可不是巧合
Well, hardly a coincidence.
然而有一些人会选择陷入忧郁
Whereas others might have succumbed to depression or...
或者滥用毒品 而这些人却把内心的忧虑
or drug abuse, these men and women have channeled their angst
转化为积极的思绪
into something positive.
谁能来做评价呢?
Who's to judge?
但有件事我可能要对你做评价
Though the one thing I might judge you on
那就是你让托尼担任新闻媒体的联系员
is your choice of Tony as liaison to the press.
你在打算着什么 杰瑟罗?
What are you up to, Jethro?
谢谢你 谢谢你
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
你们可以不用鼓掌了
You can all hold your applause.
我们为啥可以不用鼓掌了?
For what are we not applauding?
我发现了与花店保险箱上吻合的指纹
I got a hit on the DNA from the flower-shop safe.
他叫菲利克斯 昆提罗
His name is Felix Quintero.
曾做过街头小太保
He was a small-time hood
但现在已经洗手不干了
but seems to have cleaned up his act.
那他现在呢?
So, what's he doing now?
好好听着吧
You're gonna love this.
锁匠
Locksmith
他的车牌和你从ICU那里得知的相符合
His license plate matches the partial you got from ICU.
看起来他就是那位醉酒傻子
Looks like he's our drunk idiot.
把他带来
Pick him up
这就去
on it
这案子或许马上就能结了
This case may be wrapping up soon.
你就不能再见到你的前任了
You will be free from your ex.
我很好 姬娃
I am fine, zive
你看起来可不好啊
You do not seem fine.
你看起来...忧郁啊
You seem... pensive.
那是因为我早上吃了辣椒
It's the chili I had for breakfast this morning.
你知道吗 你还从没和我讲过
You know, you have never actually told me how
你俩是怎么结束的
it ended between you two.
好了 当我没问
Okay, forget I asked.
我们被跟踪了
We're being followed.
我有很不好的预感
I had a feeling, a pensive one.
刚才的掉头也证实了这点
U-turn confirmed it.
行动吧
Let's move.
NCIS 双手放方向盘上
NCIS! Hands on the wheel!
嘿 注意点
Hey, watch out!
怎么回事啊?
What is going on?
嗨 俩位
Hi, guys.
今天是个驾车的好日子 哈?
Great day for a drive, huh?
你在干什么呢?
What are you doing?
跟踪线索
Tracking down a lead.
不 我俩才是在跟踪线索
No, we're tracking down a lead.
你是在跟踪我们
You're following us.
什么?难道这犯法吗
What? Is that a crime?
是啊!
Yes!
- 准确来说 是的 - 托尼
- Technically, it is. - Tony.
听着 我只是确认能了解第一手信息
Look, I am just making sure I'm in the loop.
我说了会告诉你进展的
I told you that I would let you know.
只能说你这承诺这方面
Let's just say you don't have the best track record,
做得确实不怎么好
doing the things you say you're gonna do.
说我 你开玩笑吗?
Me?! Are you kidding?
我打给消防署吧
I'll call the fire department.
你的车都不喜欢你
Even your car doesn't like you.
我才买的啊
I just got that car.
不可能不喜欢我的
It hasn't had a chance not to like me.
车也许喜欢你 可有人并不喜欢
Well, your car may like you, but someone does not.
炸弹被接入燃油管道
It's a bomb wired into the fuel line,
在车速驶入50码是自动引爆
timed to go off when the car hit 50.
纸板做得
没错 所以证据会被烧成灰烬
Yeah, so the evidence would burn in the crash,
但制作很匆忙
but it was a rush job.
温迪突然刹车
Wendy's quick stop
导致其松散 加快了
jarred it loose, and the accelerant leaked
它接入燃油系统的速率
onto the fuel block,
之后便着火 她真幸运的
making it catch on fire. Lucky for her.
幸运 艾比 有人想杀了她
Lucky, Abbs? Someone was trying to kill her.
我只是试着乐观点嘛
I'm just trying to be positive.
嘿 准不定是托尼
Hey, maybe it was Tony.
没那可能性
Not positive.
我们找出了更多的信息
Afraid we got a little more of that.
我们发现了这个
We found this.
温迪的笔笔记
It's Wendy's notes.
一些是这个案子的 但还有一些是从
From our current case, but there's also some stuff from
有关她的报纸上截取的
old newspaper stories of hers.
还记得她说过不认识瓦里斯上校吗?
Remember she said she didn't know Captain Wallace?
恩
Yeah.
根据她的笔记
Well, according to her notes,
她曾和他一起合作过几次
she's worked with him several times in the past.
意味着...
Which means...
她骗了我们
She lied to us.
米勒小姐 我只问你一遍
Miss Miller, I'm only gonna ask you once.
你和瓦里斯上校相识多久了?
How long did you know Captain Wallace?
讲过了 我不认识他
I told you, I didn't.
根据你的笔记 之前你报导过三则新闻
According to your files, he was a source
而他正是消息来源
on three prior news articles of yours.
我是个记者 而这些是特权文件
I am a reporter! These are privileged documents!
你没有权利看我的笔记
You have no right to look through my notes.
你的笔记
Your notes
正是这起谋杀案件的证据 温迪
are evidence in an attempted murder, Wendy.
谋杀你的案件
Yours.
我只是在揭露有关浪费军方开支的报道
I was doing an expose on wasteful military spending.
瓦里斯当时提供线索
Wallace was a source.
如果告诉你们我认识他
If I told you I knew him,
你们肯定会查出来的
you'd figure that out.
记者不能揭露他们的线人 不管他生死与否
Reporters do not reveal their sources, dead or alive.
她说实话了没 蒂诺佐探员?
Is she telling the truth, Agent DiNozzo?
抱歉 什么?
I'm sorry. What?
我刚得知你和米勒女士的情史
Just found out about your history with Miss Miller.
有关这个我们稍后详谈
And we'll talk about that later.
我想你也许能辨认出来
I figured you might have some incite.
哦 呃..
Oh. Um...
是
Yeah.
她说的都是真的
She's... she's telling the truth.
瓦里斯死之前为何会打给你?
Why did Wallace call you before he was killed?
我想他可能又有什么线索
Well, I assumed he had a lead on another story.
但我真的不知道
But I really don't know.
这我没说假话
I-I didn't lie about that.
你肯定知道什么内幕
Well, you obviously know something.
有人想谋杀你
There was an attempt on your life.
我发现了 有嫌疑的人吗?
I noticed. You got a suspect?
我们对他的公寓实行监视
We're staking out his apartment.
直到我们找到他 我们可以...
Until we find him, we can...
对我实行保护性监护
Place me in protective custody.
让我进可能地不要插手此事?
And keep me as far away from this story as possible?
不可能
Forget it.
我有藏身的地方 我会没事的
I got a place to lay low. I'll be fine.
这我相信 但我
I don't doubt that,, but I'm going to have
还是坚持
to insist on sending an agent
派遣一个探员送你回去
to escort you to your destination.
蒂诺佐探员
Agent DiNozzo,
考虑你俩的关系 你要愿意
given the circumstances, if you'd like,
我可以派戴维探员
I can assign Agent David.
不可能
No way in hell.
没事的 我搞得定
It's ok. I got it.
你渴了?
You thirsty?
要吃点什么吗?
Can I get you something to eat?
我不饿
Not hungry.
你什么时候会不饿了?
Since when are you not hungry?
人都有不饿的时候
People get not hungry. It happens.
对你来说 才不是
Not to you, it doesn't.
好了 我看得出来
Okay, I can tell.
你有事想说
There is something on your mind.
你还在因为我跟踪你那事生气啊
Are you still pissed at me because I followed you?
没 只是对你笔记里一些事深感好奇
No, just curious about something I read in your notes.
那些你不应该去看的笔记
Notes that you were not supposed to read.
你报导了一起有关海军承包商的事
You were doing a story on a navy contractor.
笔记上说你需要一些内部消息
Your notes said that you needed some inside info.
两天后 你便邀请我去圣诞早午餐会
Two days later, you invited me to a Christmas brunch.
巧合吗? 我可不认为是
Coincidence? I don't think so.
你不想见我 你想利用我
You didn't want to see me. You wanted to use me.
利用我榨取内部消息
Squeeze me for some info on your guy.
你还真相信那个?
Do you really believe that?
我想错了吗
Tell me I'm wrong.
你没想错
You're not wrong.
这可不好办了
That's not cool.
反正你放了我的鸽子
Well, you blew me off anyway,
这也不好办啊
and that's not cool.
我九年都没见到你了
I haven't seen you in nine years.
从订婚结束那晚
We haven't spoken
我们就没有讲过话
since the night our engagement ended.
所以我俩更有理由叙旧了
All the more reason to catch up.
而你并不像叙旧
You didn't want to catch up.
你当时在跟进一个新闻
You were after a story,
就像Howard Hawkes电影里
like some hard-boiled word-slinger
无情的雇佣文人一样
from a Howard Hawkes movie.
我有工作要做
I had a job to do.
哼
Hmm.
你怎么了
What happened to you?
你以前可是个天真可人的孩子
You used to be such a sweet, innocent kid.
说我 那你呢?
Me? What about you?
你以前可是个无可救药的浪漫家
You used to be a hopeless romantic.
而现在你就像"十一罗汉"里的
And now you're like George Clooney
"十一罗汉"里的乔治・克鲁尼
from Ocean's Eleven.
你喜欢乔治・克鲁尼
You like George Clooney?
他有点老气过时了
I think he's a bit of a cliché.
嗯
Hmm.
金匙叶草
Golden Flower
我喜欢你抹这个香水
I love it when you wear that.
我知道
I know.
嗨 妈妈
Hi, Mom.
哦 嗨 宝贝
Oh, hi! Baby.
嘿 呃...
Hey. Um...
记得我和你说过的蒂诺佐探员吗?
you remember me telling you about Agent DiNozzo?
他 来护送我们去奶奶家
He's, uh, going to help take us to Grandma's.
蒂诺佐探元 这是我的儿子 弗雷德
Agent DiNozzo, this is my son, Fred.
嘿 弗雷德
Hey, Fred.
这是他的保姆 蒂娜
And his nanny, Tina.
嗨 蒂娜
Hi, Tina.
蒂娜 你来帮我收拾下行李吧?
So, Tina, you think you could help me pack?
我们马上就下来
We'll be down in a minute.
好的
Yeah. Okay.
别磨太久了
Don't take too long.
老妈们 没办法哈
Moms, right?
蒂娜看起来不错啊
Tina seems nice.
多好的名字
It's a good name.
蒂娜・特纳(摇滚教母) 蒂娜・费(编剧 演员)
Tina Turner. Tina Fey.
嘿 你喜欢那个哈利波特吗?
Hey, you like that Harry Potter?
他很有趣的哦
He's pretty fun,
他的魔杖还有魔法的那些东西
with his wand and the magic stuff.
要是给你选 你最喜欢的是
If you had to pick, which would you say
哪部哈利波特
is your favorite Harry Potter?
哈利没有亲吻我老妈那部
The one where Harry wasn't kissing my mom.
你看见了啊?
You saw that?
断了这念头吧
Don't let it happen again.
给你
Here you go.
哦!
Ooh!
我有错过什么吗?
I miss anything?
没发现昆提罗的身影
Well, no sign of Quintero.
哥 我饿死了
Man, am I starving.
呃
Umm.
你没给自己买点什么吗?
What, you didn't get yourself something?
我不饿
Not hungry.
从啥时开始你会不饿了?
Since when are you not hungry?
是人都有不饿的时候
People get not hungry!
天啊
Geez.
抱歉 我只是 呃...
Sorry. I just, uh...
只是...
I'm just...
真的很郁闷
Really pensive.
混乱
Confused.
为什么?
Why?
因为你今天和前任搞在一起了?
'Cause you made out with your ex-fiancée today?
什么?
What?
你在说什么呢?
What are you talking about?
唇膏 她用的就那颜色
Lipstick-- her color.
哦 你有双尖锐的鹰眼啊
Oh. Eagle eye, McGee.
你在烦什么?
So what's the problem?
她离婚了 你是单身
She's divorced. You're single.
问题是 我曾经历过这一切
Problem is, been there, done that.
结局还不是很失败
Crash-burn.
有这么坏吗?
That bad?
运输安全委员会还在寻找尸体
NTSB's still looking for bodies.
发生什么事了?
Yeah, what happened?
问得好 麦基
That's a good question, McGee.
你的问题总是很犀利
You always ask the good questions.
好啊 那你想怎么样
Okay, so what do you want to happen?
沉默代表咱得换个话题了
Cue the subject change.
和你讲 那个女人在那站了
You know, that woman's been standing over there for...
有一段时间恶劣
quite some time.
外面可是很冷的
It's pretty cold out.
我要去和她谈谈
I'm going to go talk to her.
嘿
Hey there.
有时间聊下吗?
You have the time?
我的表坏了 而且...
My watch is on the fritz, and...
嘿
Hey.
你要去哪  你有什么毛病啊?
Where you going? What's the matter with you?
NCIS!
逃跑是无益的 给我回来
It's no good running away. Come back here!
麦基
McGee!
你要去哪 嗷
You going somewhere? Ow!
别这样啊
Come on.
看来你没听说过NCIS啊
Guess you never heard of NCIS.
哥俩是警察 徽章在这啊
We're cops. Look at our badges.
哦 看见了
Oh. There it is.
听着 兄弟 我们只是...
Look, man, we were just...
超级英雄派诱饵吸引罪犯
Bait patrol.
我知道 好不
Yeah, I know. Yeah.
我要逮捕你们所有的人
I'm going to arrest all of you.
什么 我们可是搭档啊!
What? We're... we're coworkers!
你看见她脖子上的东西没?
Do you see what was on his neck?
你如果指的是Soulless纹身 当然看见了
If you're talking about Soulless's tattoo, yeah.
你们听说过我? 或者我应该说
You guys heard of me? Or should I say
菲利克斯 昆提罗
Felix Quintero?
嗷 别这样啊
Aw, come on, man.
之所以叫秘密身份是有原因的
There's a reason it's called a secret identity.
你难道才上小学三年级吗?
What are you, in the third grade?
你在干什么?
What are you do...?
真要这样
Really?
这可不是什么秘密身份
It's not a secret identity.
那身装扮确实很赞
That is a good outfit.
谢谢你 麦基
Thank you, McGee.
好了 走吧
All right, let's move.
证物库你的女士们先生们注意啦
Ladies and gentlemen of the evidence garage,
我给你们请来了Whipcord
I bring you Whipcord.
Spandaxia 看着不错哇
Spandaxia, looking good.
嗨 闪电侠
Hey there, Bolt.
看着啊
Check this out.
嘿 那不是玩具
Hey, that's not a toy.
那是声波诱敌武器
It's a sonic diversionary weapon.
用来混淆敌人方向感的
Used to disorient the enemy.
我们是来帮忙的
You know, we're here to help.
我们需要你们给点职业上的尊敬
We'd appreciate a little professional courtesy.
你们不是职业人员
You are not professionals.
嘿 头儿
Hey, boss.
我不需要这个的
I don't need this.
在你做出评论前 请记住哦
Before you judge, just remember,
如果事情出什么变故
if things had gone differently,
那全是麦基的错
this could have been McGee.
疑犯在哪?
Where's the suspect?
哦 多纳盖特带他审问去了
Oh. Dorneget brought him up to interrogation.
我们将带这些人去会议室做笔录报告
We'll be debriefing these guys in the conference room.
你肯定是管事的人了
You must be in charge.
我是Spandaxia
I'm Spandaxia.
Boltcutter
Boltcutter.
Whipcord!
好吧
All right.
再上楼前 把你的牛鞭上交给我
Hand over the bullwhip
还有你的钳子
and the bolt cutter before you go upstairs.
哇哦
Wow.
多酷的铁面侠啊 头儿
Remarkable straight face, boss.
知道吗 你想咋笑就笑吧
You know, laugh all you want,
但街道是个危险之地
but the streets are a dangerous place.
你们最多也就是在事发后做些调查
All you do is investigate after something happens.
自从我们开始巡逻 这个地区的犯罪率
Since we've been patrolling, crime in our area
已经下降了50%
is down 50%.
我们让你们的工作轻松多了
Yeah, we make your job easier.
实际上 姬娃会让我们的工作很轻松
Actually, Ziva would make our job easier.
她在哪 我们
Where is she? We could use
需要她帮忙问一下话
a little help with the interviews.
她正带那记者来看
She's bringing in the reporter to see
能否认出昆提罗
if she can ID Quintero.
姬娃和温迪单独呆在一块
Ziva's alone with Wendy?
这可不妙啊
That's not good.
他们来了吗 来了吗 来了吗吗
Are they here? Are they here? Are they here?
哇哦
Whoa.
现实生活的超级英雄
Real-Life Superheroes.
能和你们合个影吗?
Can I get a picture with you guys?
当然了
Of course.
来吧
Come on.
超炫的道服啊
Great costume.
哦
Oh.
我没穿道服
This isn't my costume.
我只穿了普通的衣服
These are just my... clothes.
哦
Oh.
见没 这就是我不能让你俩
See, this I could do without.
我不知道托尼会晕车
I did not know Tony got motion sick.
等他没吃药的时候你就会发现的
Well, uh, you would if he wasn't on his meds.
嗨
Hi.
你怎么样了?
So... how's things?
很好 你呢?
Good. You?
说实话 我...
Actually, I will...
其实 我得走了
You know what? I'm going to go.
我得去照顾弗雷德
Because I need to get back to Fred.
哦 帮说声好啊 顺便
Oh, who says hello, by the way.
呃 我觉得他喜欢你
Hm. I think he likes you.
哼
Hmm.
好吧 我准备好听了
Okay, let's hear it.
听什么?
Hear what?
我确定她肯定说了什么
I'm sure she said something.
有什么值得告诉我的内幕?
Is there something to tell?
哦
Oh.
哦 我看得出来 咱俩还是很像的
Oh, I can see you and I are a lot alike.
大男人的行为 寡言少语
Both men of action, few words.
杰克・瓦里斯上校
Captain Jack Wallace.
德克斯特・墨菲
Dexter Murphy.
罪案现场找到了你的DNA
Your DNA was found at the crime scene.
电话回复机上也出现了你威胁的话语
And your voice was on the answering machine making threats.
你认为我的凶手
You think I'm the killer?
太荒谬了!
This is nuts!
为什么我要杀死
Why on Earth-616 would I kill
自己的超级英雄同伴?
my fellow superheroes?
我可不想惹上麻烦 你不想惹麻烦?
I don't want any trouble! You don't want any trouble?
不! 真糟糕 是你找到的
No! Too bad 'cause you found it!
你个傻子 是你找到的! 让他走吧!
No, punk, you found it! Let him go!
很欣赏你的诚实
Appreciate the honesty.
实际上 温迪也这么说你的
Actually, that is something Wendy mentioned about you.
你是她所认识的最诚实的人呢
That you were one of the most honest people she knew.
真的吗?
Really?
对别人很诚实
To others.
她说你只对自己会撒谎
She said the only person you lie to is yourself.
而且还是经常性的
Which she says you do a lot.
哈 这个...
Huh, well...
精彩爆了
That was awesome.
但你却想错了
But you got it all wrong.
这段录像是安排好的
That video was staged.
Code和Solanum队长雇我安排的那出袭击
Captain Code and Solanum hired me to fake that attack.
没人知道 甚至录像师
Nobody knew, not even the cameraman.
为什么?
Why?
宣传啊 知道不
Publicity, duh.
他们想成立自己的超级英雄团
They wanted to start their own superhero league.
如今大家伙都有自己的团了
Everyone's got a league these days;
团结社区什么的
there's a unity in the community.
多好的名字啊
That's a great league name.
团结社区
Unity in the Community.
我喜欢莱文沃思
I like Leavenworth.
这样的 他们至今还没给我雇佣费
Look, they never paid me for the video.
我也不知道他们真名
And I didn't know their real names,
所以我就查了下 留下那短信
so I tracked them down, and I left that message.
然后就去要回我的钱
Then I came back later to get my money.
瓦里斯和墨菲早已死了
Wallace and Murphy were already dead.
没错
Yep.
然后 你就洗劫了那地
So, you robbed the place.
准确地说 那钱是属于我的
Technically, the money I took was mine.
嘿 知道我为啥自封Soulless(灵魂缺失者)
Hey, why do you think I call myself Soulless?
但 我不是什么杀手
But... I am not a killer.
我留下那通语音时人还没到城里
I was halfway across town when I left that voice mail,
Toln退休中心那有50个人
and there's 50 gramass at Toln Retirement Center
可以为我作证呢
that can vouch for me.
我谁也没杀
I didn't kill anybody.
退休中心的管理主任
Well, the administrator at the retirement center
确实了昆提罗不在场的证据
confirmed Quintero's alibi.
Soulless在星期二晚上参加了一个魔术表演
Soulless does a magic show for the residents on Tuesday nights.
他不是我们要找的人
He's not our guy.
我们该看看其他的超级英雄们
We should look at other superheroes.
呃 也许有人嫉妒
Uh, maybe someone was getting jealous
瓦里斯所得的光彩
of all the attention Wallace was getting.
调查记者的档案
Link was the reporter.
我不知道 头儿
Well, I don't know, boss.
我想的是其他一些天使们
I can think of a bunch of other angles.
好吧 这档案是咱们那位记者的
Okay, the link is the reporter.
来继续谈谈她吧
Let's keep talking about her.
我们知道她参与了
We know she was working on
几次告密者活动
several whistle- blower stories
和瓦里斯一起
with Wallace.
也许他们揭发的信息有误
Well, maybe they blew the wrong whistle.
或者打算揭露个不一样的内幕
Or were about to blow a different one.
温迪说瓦里斯在他死的前一天
Wendy said that Wallace called her
给她打了电话
the day before he was killed.
可能是他发现了一些新的线索
Perhaps he was onto something new.
姬娃 再去联系下他的指挥官
Ziva, talk to his C.O. again.
麦基 把有关她的那些新闻找来
McGee, get me those old news stories.
我会整合成一个文件
I'll put together a file.
蒂诺佐
DiNozzo.
知道 检查温迪的电话记录
I know. Go through Wendy's phone records
然后联系那些在过去的六个月里
and talk to every guy she's spoken with
跟她说过话的每一个人
in the last six months.
不是 我已经弄了
No. I got that.
达克打来了 下楼去 看看他想要些什么
Ducky called. Go down, see what he wants.
谢谢你 头儿
Thank you, boss.
你好
Hello.
我还以为吉布斯会来
I was expecting Gibbs.
他让我来
He sent me.
你发现了什么
What do you got?
恩 我给其他验尸员发了有关
Well, I've been e-mailing a few fellow M.E.s
这案例的邮件
about our case.
他们提供了一些有关系的信息
They've provided some pertinent information.
很难相信他们有时候会这么小
Hard to believe they're so small sometimes.
托尼 你在想些什么
What's on your mind, Tony?
你有点愁眉苦脸的
You sound a little pensive.
我没有
I am not pensive!
为什么每个人都这样说 我
What is it with everyone and that word?! I...
不好意思
Sorry.
我只是
I'm just...
你介不介意谈一下
Would you care to talk about it?
你有没有遇到过很恐怖的事 然后你觉得
You ever had something terrible happen and then you think
你早已将其置之身后 但恐惧又再次出现
you put it all behind you, but then the terrible comes back
并且变得比以前更加令人害怕
and it's more terrible than it was before?
我现在很困扰
I'm confused.
我也是
So am I.
托尼 从认识你的第一天
Tony, it was very clear to me from the very first day
我就深知你是个情场曲折的人
that I met you that you were a man in pain.
对不起 我觉得你把我
I'm sorry, I think you have me
跟别人弄混了
confused with someone else.
不 在我看来 你的痛苦和杰瑟罗一样
No, your pain was as clear to me as Jethro's.
他失去了莎侬 他一生的挚爱
He lost Shannon, the one love of his life,
而你则是因纷繁复杂的原因失去了信仰
and you lost faith in yourself for so many reasons.
杰瑟罗选择不停地和别人结婚
Jethro coped with his pain by
来掩埋这份痛楚
repeatedly marrying the wrong woman,
这也造成他最终会孤身一人的结局
thus insuring that ultimately he would be alone
并且永远心痛
and safe from heartbreak.
你是重复地追逐错误的对象
You repeatedly chase the wrong woman.
你现在很孤独是因为 你没能做到 如你所说
You're alone because you never did, as you just said,
将其抛之于脑后
put it all behind you.
当温迪在结婚前一夜
When Wendy told me the night before
告诉我取消婚礼时
we were supposed to get married that she was calling it off,
我完全不能接受
I didn't take it very well.
我们有九年都没有说过话了
We hadn't spoken in nine years,
直到昨天
until yesterday.
好了 也许命运在给你一个去完结的机会
Well, perhaps fate has given you another chance at closure.
又或者其他
Or something else.
不是命运 是吉布斯
It's not fate, it's Gibbs.
他在整我
Dude set me up.
验尸官说了什么
What did the M.E. have to say?
我们交流了一下
Uh, we exchanged notes on
这些超级英雄的生活动向
the Real-Life Superhero movement.
结果是
It turns out,
这家伙于几个月前在临近的街区被人杀害
one was killed in the next district several months ago.
我做了一些调查 发现另一起也是谋杀
I did some checking and found another was murdered
而且时间还更早
sometime before that.
因此 这些要么是
Ergo, either these are the result
由于高危工作造成的 或者
of a very dangerous line of work or...
有人杀了超级英雄么
Somebody's killing Superheroes?
说吧
Talk to me.
我们汇编整理了下机器谋杀案件的资料
We compiled the case data on the different murders.
4个受害者 三个罪案现场
Four victims, three crime scenes.
首先 这看起来并没有可以考察的地方 亲们
At first, it looks like nothing to see here, folks.
目击者声称前两名受害者
The witnesses said that the first two victims
是在值勤时被杀害的
were killed in the line of duty.
值勤
Duty?
karma公爵
Lord of Karma
是在想阻止一起盗窃行为时被枪击
was shot trying to foil a burglary.
Feverblister是在想要阻止劫车而被刺死
Feverblister was stabbed trying to stop a carjacking.
很不寻常的作案手法
Very different MO's.
但是你提到了一种模式
But you noticed a pattern.
你注意到了我们都注意到的东西
And you noticed that we noticed.
这就是为什么我们有所进展
And that is why we all get along.
现在 每次你带着手机走进一个新的地区
Now, every time you move into a new area with a cell phone,
它都会提醒当地的移动信号塔
it pings the local cell tower.
结果 这个相同的手机出现在
Bottom line, the same cell phone shows up
每一个谋杀现场的附近
in each neighborhood where a murder took place.
这就说明 同一个人
Which means, so does the same person,
出现在几乎相同的时间
at almost the exact same time.
谁
Who?
我们的赢家是
Our winner is...
克莱恩斯・托百特!
Clarence Tobett!
别名ICU
Aka ICU.
看起来托尼是对的
Looks like Tony was right.
头儿 我想他是在比赛中被杀死的
Boss, I think he's been killing the competition.
我不觉得
I don't.
你不能穿着这一身出这个房间
You are not going out of this house in that outfit!
至少不能在大白天
Not in the day!
欧 才怪
Yes, I am.
只要我完成了我的招数
As soon as I finish my Mook Yan Chong kata!
不 实际上 你没有
No, actually, you're not.
噢 天啊 他又犯了什么事儿
Oh, dear Lord, what did he do now?
我们发现了一部属于凶手的手机
We found a cell phone belonging to the murderer.
上面注册是你儿子的名字
It's registered in your son's name.
你们这种行为冒犯了我
I'm offended by insinuation...
住嘴
Shut up!
你再敢说一个字
Don't you say one more word.
把我们的律师叫来
Call our lawyer.
不 我们帮你叫
No, we'll call for you.
姬娃
Ziva.
嗯哼
Mm-hmm.
吉布斯探员 我是把很多人都送进重症监护室
Agent Gibbs, I put plenty of people in the ICU,
但我保证 他们都是罪有应得
but I assure you they all deserved...
闭上你的鸟嘴
Shut up!
你根本就没有送任何人进重症监护室
You didn't put anybody in the ICU.
你只是
All you do is
给医院生病的小孩送了点玩具
give toys to sick kids in hospitals.
你真的是太可悲了
You're pathetic.
哦哦 那是我打的
Oops, that's me.
肯定是拨错了电话号码
Must have dialed the wrong number.
你刚刚拨了什么号码
What number did you dial?
凶手的
The murderer's.
额
Ah.
让我猜猜
Let me guess.
公司电话
Company phone?
你记在你儿子名下的公司
A company you keep in your son's name
作为避税的 对吧
for tax purposes, right?
给我闭嘴 汤姆
Don't you say one thing, Tom.
我们倒是无所谓
That's actually okay with us,
因为你们都有权利保持沉默
because you both have the right to remain silent.
ICU就免了 但是吧
Not quite the ICU, but...
我也想试试
Works for me.
干得好
Nice job.
维恩・托百特是个房产大亨
Wayne Tobett was a slumlord.
他喜欢在犯罪率很高的地段买下便宜的楼盘
His specialty was buying cheap buildings in crime-ridden areas.
犯罪率越高越好
More crime, the better.
房产的价格就会更低
Property values were lowered.
他最不想要的 就是在他看中的地段
The last thing he needed where he was looking to buy
出现社区超级英雄监察团体
was a community watch program on steroids.
但超级英雄偏巧喜欢出没在那
But that's exactly what the Real-Life Superheroes were.
犯罪率下降了 房产价就开始上升了
Crime was down, property values were going up.
他们真的有所作为啊
They were making a difference.
听起来你改变看法了啊
Sounds like you've had a change of heart.
好人就是好人 里昂
Good guys are good guys, Leon.
是啊 坏人很坏
Yeah, bad guys are bad.
他们肯定认识到超级英雄的效应 杀了他们
Figured they'd go in and kill the Superheroes,
犯罪率就会上升 然后他又可以买到廉价物品了
the crime would go up, then they go in and buy cheap.
为什么他们想要炸死那个记者
Why'd they try to blow up the reporter?
温迪揭露了很多有关华盛顿特区房地产的内幕
Wendy had done a fluff piece on real estate in the DC area.
吉布斯探员提到过
Agent Gibbs noticed that
很多廉价房产在那交易
the areas where a lot of cheap buying was going on
同时这地区
were the same areas
正是超级英雄们遇害之地
where Superheroes were being murdered.
避免不了的
Of course he did.
买家就是维恩・托百特
Buyer's Wayne Tobett.
我们猜他越来越紧张了
We think he started getting nervous
因为温迪和我们做出同样的猜测
Wendy would make the same connection we did.
不错
Nice work.
特别是你 吉布斯探员
Especially you, Agent Gibbs.
或者我应该说丘比特
Or should I say Cupid?
毕竟今天是情人节
It is Valentine's Day, after all.
头儿 他在暗示什么?
Boss, what's he talking about?
嗨
Hey.
看看你
Well... look at you.
当我听说旺斯主管让你来犯罪现场采集图片
When I heard Director Vance was letting you take pictures
我不得不亲眼证实一下
of the crime scene, I had to see it to believe it.
当他听说我要把疯狂的海军警官的故事
Well, when he heard I changed my story from crazy naval officer
换成杀死社区英雄的房产大亨时
to evil slumlord that killed a dedicated community activist,
他墙裂支持啊
he got very agreeable.
恩
Mm.
很喜欢你的靴子
Really like those boots.
谢谢啊
Thank you very much.
我们在暗示你退下了 博思寇
That's your cue to leave, Bosco.
谢谢
Thank you, sir.
那个人
That guy.
看起来 看起来
Look... Look...
那么 我 恩 那么
So, I... Hmm. So...
或许我们应该一个一个地说吧
Maybe we should take turns.
女士优先
Ladies first.
我对你说谎了 托尼
I lied to you, Tony.
关于啥
About?
为什么我邀请去早午餐
Why I invited you to brunch.
你错了 我并不是想要得到那个故事的信息
You were wrong; I was not trying to get information for a story.
我要请你是因为我想要见到你
I invited you because I wanted to see you.
该你了
Your turn.
为什吗
Why?
呃 因为我们要轮流着来啊 现在该你说了
Uh, because we're taking turns, and now it's your turn.
不对 这个不是我的本意 而且你知道的
No, that is not what I meant, and you know it.
你想知道我为什么离开
You want to know why I left.
我想知道的是你为啥要对我说 是的
I want to know why you said yes to me
可答案本应该是 不
when the answer was really no.
我很想知道为何你一直等着
I want to know why you waited
直到最后才告诉我真相
until the very last minute to tell me the truth.
但最想知道的是 我的落跑新娘为何要离开
But most of all, my runaway bride, I would like to know why.
好吧 为什么现在不能做出变化呢
Well, would it make a difference now?
我的意思是 如果你不觉得很难受
I mean, if you weren't so sad
很孤单 你根本就不会去思考
and so lonely, you wouldn't even be wondering.
是
Are...
悲伤和孤独
Sad and lonely?
你是不是把我跟博思寇搞混了
You have me confused with Bosco.
你想看看我的女友小文档吗
You like to see my little black e-book?
无论你给我看什么
Show me whatever you'd like,
那都不会改变我自己亲眼看到的真相
but it's not gonna change what I see with my own eyes.
你应该告诉她你的感觉 不论她是谁
You should tell her how you feel, whoever she is.
A 那根本不会发生
A) That's not gonna happen.
B 离开我的视界
B) Get out of my head.
还有C 回答这个问题
And C) answer the question.
我离开 是因为没准备好去见他 你懂吗
I left because I wasn't ready to meet the one, okay?
而你就是那个他
And you were the one.
这根本就说不过去
That doesn't make any sense.
你确定
Are you sure?
因为在我看来
'Cause from what I see,
你花了过去九年半的时间
you've spent the last nine-and-a-half years
逃避现实的关系
avoiding real relationships.
我最开始只是伤心
I was just broken first.
这就是为什么我离开了我的英雄警察 然后跟一个
Which is why I left my hero cop and married a stockbroker
只关心钱不关心人的股票经纪人结婚了
who cared more about money than people.
我当初并未做好面对他的准备 托尼
I wasn't ready to meet the one when we met, Tony.
但我送去邀请是因为...
But I sent you that invitation because...
我现在准备好了
I am now.